ACTWU Communications and Public Relations Department Burt Beck Files 5619/027
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Clippings, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  August-December
- Clippings, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Jan.-Feb.
- Clippings, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  March
- Clippings, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  April
- Clippings, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Clippings, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Clippings, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Clippings, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Clippings, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Clippings, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  October
- Clippings, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  November
- Clippings, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  December
- Clippings, 1974; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  January
- Clippings, 1974; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  February
- Clippings, 1974; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Clippings, 1974; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  April-May
- Clippings, 1974; Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Clippings, 1974; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  July-December
- Clippings, 1975-1978; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Clippings, 1979; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  January- June
- Clippings, 1979; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Clippings, 1980; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Clippings, 1980; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Clippings, 1981-1983; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Clippings, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Clippings, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  No Date; Folder 1 of 2
- Clippings, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  No date; Folder 2 of 2
- Stationary, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Notes, Speeches, and Statements, 1980; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Notes, Speeches, and Statements, 1981; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Notes, Speeches, and Statements, 1982; Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Notes, Speeches, and Statements, 1983; Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Notes, Speeches, and Statements, 1984; Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Ads and Resolutions, 1976; Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Ads and Resolutions, 1977; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Ads and Resolutions, 1978; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Ads and Resolutions, 1974; Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Ads and Resolutions, 1980; Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Ads and Resolutions, 1981; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Ads and Resolutions, 1982; Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Ads and Resolutions, 1983; Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Ads and Resolutions, 1984; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens and Co. Board and Court Cases, 1951-1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  v. 1; Folder 1 of 2
- J.P. Stevens and Co. Board and Court Cases, 1951-1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  v.1; (Folder 2 of 2)
- J.P. Stevens and Co. Board and Court Cases, 1951-1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  v.1; (Folder 1 of 2); Copy 2
- J.P. Stevens and Co. Board and Court Cases, 1951-1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  v.1; (Folder 2 of 2); Copy 2
- J.P. Stevens and Co. Board and Court Cases, 1951-1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  v.2; (Folder 1 of 2)
- J.P. Stevens and Co. Board and Court Cases, 1951-1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  v.2; (Folder 2 of 2)
- J.P. Stevens and Co. Board and Court Cases, 1976-1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  v.3
- ACTWU vs. J.P. Stevens Co. Case 77 Civ. 5444 (CSH), 1978-1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
- US Court of Appeals NLRB vs. J.P. Stevens, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
- US Court of Appeals ACWA vs. NLRB, Farah vs. NLRB, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
- House of Representatives. Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations ACTWU Testimony, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Statement of ACTWU. Senate Subcommittee on Human Resources, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Statement of ACTWU. Senate Subcommittee on Human Resources, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Statement of ACTWU. Senate Subcommittee on Human Resources, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
- US Foreign Policy Towards the Philippines, 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
- James Johnson. Hearing Officer's Report Tidewate Joint Board, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Hearing Officer's Report Textile Division, Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Chicago, IL
- Farah vs. ACWA Case No. 23-CA-4435, 1974; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Transcripts Unknown, Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  pp.16-45
- Transcripts. Unknown, Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Tape 1-5
- Transcripts Unknown, Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Tape 2
- Transcripts. Unknown, Publication (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Tapes 2-3; pp.1-54
- Transcripts. Unknown, Publication (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Tape 1; pp1- 64
- Transcripts. Unknown, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Tape 2, Side 1; pp. 1-23. Tape 3, Side 2; pp.1-5
- Transcripts. Unknown, Publication (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Tape 2, Sides 1-2; pp. 1-51
- Transcripts. Awards Ceremony. Jacob Timmerman, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Transcripts. Convention. Tuesday Morning Session, 1981; Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  pp. 80-115, 375-501, 551-562, 594- 597
- Transcripts. Farah Audio Tape, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Transcripts. GEB, 1982; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  March 8
- Transcripts. GEB, 1982; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  March 8; Copy 2
- Transcripts. GEB, 1982; Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  July 28-29
- Transcripts. GEB, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Transcripts. GEB. Philadelphia, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Transcripts. Scott Hoyman, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Transcripts. Problems S.S. Systems, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  pp. 250-302
- Transcripts. Referees Dinne. St. Regis, 1982; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Transcripts. Sol Stetin, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  pp. 3A-1 - 3B-57
- Transcripts. Orphaned Pages., Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Statements. E.J. Donnelly, 1983; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
- In Memoriam/ Eulogies, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Inter-Office Memoranda, Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens. Foreign., Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens. Letter to Employees, 1976; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  June 8
- J.P. Stevens. Profits Over People, Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens. Weekly Activity Reports., 1975-1976; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Letters. Drafts., 1975-1976; Publication (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Lists, Questionnaires, etc., Publication (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Mailing Services., 1976-1978; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Notes on a Program to Promote ACTWU Label, Publication (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Press Kit: Norma Rae, Publication (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Printing Costs, 1983; Publication (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Margaret Quesdada. Farah Striker., Publication (Box 6, Folder 27)
- R. Joseph. Harrill and Farr. Multi Media and Public Relations Campaign Proposal., 1981; Publication (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Responses to Points Made in Heritage Foundation Report, Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Jack Salem. Resume of Dr. Polling's Press Conference, Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Social Justice. Articles. Drafts., Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Social Justice. Current., 1977-1978; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Social Justice. Publication Materials., 1977-1978; Publication (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Staff Union Contract, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Sol Stein. 72nd Birthday, Publication (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Subscription, Publication (Box 6, Folder 36)
- TWUA Presidents Room. Dedication., 1981; Publication (Box 6, Folder 37)
  Sept. 26
- Video Production, 1980-1981; Publication (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Betty Ziff. Convention Freelance Writer, 1983; Publication (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Orphaned Pages, Publication (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Statements. Testimonies of Herman Rebhan, 1983; Publication (Box 6, Folder 41)
  May 4
- Statements. Howard D. Samuel, 1983; Publication (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Statements. Jacob Sheinkman, 1978; Publication (Box 6, Folder 43)
  Jan. 25
- Statements. Jacob Sheinkman, 1978; Publication (Box 6, Folder 44)
  May 15
- Statements. Jacob Sheinkman, 1983; Publication (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Statements. Jacob Sheinkman, 1983; Publication (Box 6, Folder 46)
  May 5
- Statements. Sol Stein on the Need for Labor Law Reform, 1977; Publication (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Statements. B.R. Skelton, Publication (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Statements. Marc Stepp, 1983; Publication (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Advertising Copy, 1974; Publication (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Frank Blechman, Publication (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Burl Johnson and Associates, Publication (Box 6, Folder 52)
- John Chupka, Publication (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Circular Letters to Members, Publication (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Circular Letters to Staff, Publication (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Constitution Galleys, 1984; Publication (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Cotton Dust/ Brown Lung, 1977-1981; Publication (Box 6, Folder 57)
- George Dillman, Publication (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Film. 60 Minutes, 1979-1980; Publication (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Film. MacNeil-Lehrer Report, 1977-1980; Publication (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Film. Testimony, Publication (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Angelo Georgian, Publication (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Bob Hall. J.P. Stevens Stockholder, 1975-1976; Publication (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Original Source, 1979; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Original Source Material, 1979; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Original Source Material, 1980; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Jan.- Feb.
- Original Source Material. Labor Unity, 1980; Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Source Material., 1980; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Original Source Material, 1980; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Source Material, 1980; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Original Source Material, 1980; Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Original MSS, 1980; Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Original Source Material, 1980; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Aug
- Original Source Material, 1980; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Sept.
- Original Source Material, 1980; Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Original Source Material, 1980; Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Nov.
- Original Source Material, 1980; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Dec.
- Original Source Material, 1982; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Feb.
- Original Source Material, 1982; Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Original Source Material, 1982; Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Original Source Material, 1982; Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Original Source Material, 1982; Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Original Source Material, 1982; Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Aug.
- Original Source Material, 1982; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Original Source Material, 1982; Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Oct.
- Original Source Material, 1982; Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Original Source Material, 1982; Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Original Source Material, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Jan.
- Original Source Material, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Original Source Material, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Original Source Material, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Apr
- Original Source Material, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Original Source Material, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Original Source Material, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Original Source Material, 1983; Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Original Source Material, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Original Source Material, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Oct
- Original Source Material, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Original Source Material, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Original Source Material, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Original Source Material, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Original Source Material, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Original Source Material, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Original Source Material, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Original Source Material, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Original Source Material, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
  July/Aug.
- Original Source Material, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Original Source Material, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Original Source Material, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Original Source Material, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Assignments, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Assignments, 1982; Publication (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Assignments, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Assignments, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Assignments, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Assignments, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Assignments, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Assignments, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Assignments, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Assignments, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Assignments, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Assignments, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Assignments, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Assignments, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Assignments, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 30)
  July/Aug
- Assignments, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Assignments, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Assignments, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Assignments, 1984; Publication (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Election Notices, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Election Notices, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Election Notices, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Election Notices, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Election Notices, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Election Notices, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Election Notices, 1983; Publication (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Election Notices, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Election Notices, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Election Notices, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Election Notices, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Election Notices, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Election Notices, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Election Notices, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Election Notices, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Election Notices, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Election Notices, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Election Notices, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Dec
- English, 1983; Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
- English, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Jan
- Pages, 1982; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Photos & Art Work, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Photos & Art Work, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Photos & Art Work, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Photos & Art Work, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Photos & Art Work, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Photos and Art, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO Resolutions, Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
- American Have a Heart, Publication (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Billboards, Publication (Box 10, Folder 23)
- CBS Evening News, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Chronological Listing of the Developments in the Farah Strike, Publication (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Convention. Joint Board Index, 1984; Publication (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Correspondences. General., Publication (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Court Records, Publication (Box 10, Folder 28)
- This is the Amalgamated, Publication (Box 10, Folder 29)
- El Paso, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Farah Fact Sheet, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 31)
- The Farah Story: La Huelga (The Strike), Publication (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Farah Statements, Publication (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Farah Strike Emerges as Struggle for Basic Rights, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Farah Strike Supports. Churches., Publication (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Farah Strike Support. General, Publication (Box 10, Folder 36)
- William Farah. Correspondence., Publication (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Nick Galifianakis, Publication (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Graphics, Publication (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Imports Demonstration Day, 1981; Publication (Box 10, Folder 40)
- J.P. Stevens and the Heritage Foundation, Publication (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Letters to Editors, Publication (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Men's Wear Publication, Publication (Box 10, Folder 43)
- National Labor Relations Act. Section 10(j)., Publication (Box 10, Folder 44)
- National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Newspaper Ads, Publication (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Jacob S. Potofsky Biography, Publication (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Proposal for a Fact-Finding Commission, Publication (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Jacob Sheinkman. Biography, Publication (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Southern California Joint Board Press Release, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Newspaper Clippings, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Name and address file, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Loose 3x5 index cards